How do you get even with a womanizer? Make him a woman!
Sam is a comedy, fantasy, romance film directed by Nicholas Brooks.
The journey of young, handsome New York City playboy Sam Wellman - man’s man and
professional woman hater – and his relationship with Doc, his best (and only!) friend.
One strange, drunken night Sam stumbles into an Old Curiosity Shop, where the elderly proprietor
offers him tea along with sage advice on treasuring “the female of the species”.
Sam awakens the next morning to find himself transformed into a woman.
Samantha, played by Natalie Knepp.
Sam, played by Brock Harris.
Doc, played by Sean Kleier.
Lulu, played by Morgan Fairchild.
The Shopkeeper, played by Stacy Keach.
Seymour, played by James McCaffrey.
Sam Esmail (born September 17, 1977) is an American film and television producer,
director, and screenwriter who runs the production company Esmail Corp.
He is best known as the creator, writer, and director of the
award-winning USA Network television series Mr.
Robot (2015–2019), starring Rami Malek.
He wrote and directed the feature films Comet (2014)
and Leave the World Behind (2023).
He produced and directed the first season of the acclaimed Amazon Prime Video psychological thriller Homecoming (2018–2020), starring Julia Roberts
and Janelle Monáe, and produced USA's Briarpatch (2020), Starz's Gaslit (2022), and Peacock's Angelyne (2022) and The Resort (2022).
Esmail's work often centers on the themes of
alienation, technology, and American society.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.